<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Karin Holley</title>
    <link>https://karinholley.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Karin Holley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://karinholley.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Second Article</title>
      <link>https://karinholley.com/blog/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://karinholley.com/blog/second/</guid>
      <description>My daughter painted this tree when she was about 10 years old. What is unusual about it, is that she&amp;rsquo;s given the root system just as much attention and space as the part of the tree most of us draw when we think of a &amp;ldquo;tree&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article 1</title>
      <link>https://karinholley.com/blog/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://karinholley.com/blog/first/</guid>
      <description>As a third culture kid - now adult - my survival strategy was to adapt. Adapt to the local surroundings, blend in, do as the Romans do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Karin</title>
      <link>https://karinholley.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://karinholley.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Grow Yourself to Grow Your Vision Leadership Coach for Educators
In a nutshell, I am: Curious - About the world, people, myself, how humans think, feel and behave Passionate - About sustainability, justice and equity, diversity, coaching, education, health Caring - I’m very empathetic, supporting others has always been my calling Growth-oriented - I love learning, and I constantly look for ways to improve and challenge myself Risk-taker - I follow my passion despite the challenges Experienced Transitions such as multiple career changes, working internationally, parenting, serious relationship breakups, perimenopause Mental health issues: burnout, intense loneliness, food issues, insomnia Coach, Trainer, Counsellor, Teacher Qualified Associate Certified Coach (ACC) with the International Coaching Federation Advanced Certified Professional Coach (ACA) with the International Coach Academy Positive Intelligence Certified Coach Master’s degree in Counselling Master’s degree in Teaching Let&#39;s Meet I have never met any professional so capable of being present for their client, noticing changes in their demeanour, an eyebrow or glow in their eye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGB</title>
      <link>https://karinholley.com/agb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://karinholley.com/agb/</guid>
      <description>§1 Lorem Bacon ipsum dolor amet pig pork hamburger tenderloin burgdoggen spare ribs bacon pancetta pork loin tail turducken. Chicken pastrami jerky tongue ball tip strip steak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another post about work</title>
      <link>https://karinholley.com/blog/another-post-about-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://karinholley.com/blog/another-post-about-work/</guid>
      <description>sadness don&amp;rsquo;t lose focus things will get better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fourth</title>
      <link>https://karinholley.com/blog/fourth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://karinholley.com/blog/fourth/</guid>
      <description>hello friend</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grow</title>
      <link>https://karinholley.com/grow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://karinholley.com/grow/</guid>
      <description>Grow Yourself Discover mental patterns that are blocking you from advancing your goals and vision.
Gain more clarity of mind and confidence to improve your focus and decision-making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OldGrow</title>
      <link>https://karinholley.com/grow_old/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://karinholley.com/grow_old/</guid>
      <description>You are a leader who is: Growth-oriented, idealistic, and mission-driven. In some personal and/or professional transition. Committed to personal and professional growth, but have reached the limits of what you can do by yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Success Stories</title>
      <link>https://karinholley.com/success_stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://karinholley.com/success_stories/</guid>
      <description>I started coaching with Karin to gain traction on elusive long term goals - things I&amp;rsquo;d been working on for years, but hadn&amp;rsquo;t made much progress with</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
